Guide to the Sciencenter records, 1982-2017.
Sciencenter records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Sciencenter records, 1982-2017.
6325
Sciencenter
12 cubic ft.
Manuscripts, Printed Materials, Publications, Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes log notebooks from Executive Director Charles Trautmann, annual reports, meeting minutes, newsletters, calendar of events, manuals and brochures of the Sciencenter.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
The Sciencenter, a non-profit hands-on science museum in Ithaca, New York, grew out of a volunteer-run science program at a local elementary school. Founded in 1983, the Sciencenter operated from storefronts for nearly a decade. In 1993, the museum opened the first phase of its permanent home. Phase II opened in 1996 and provided additional program space. Phase III, which opened in 2003, expanded the Sciencenter to 32,000 sq. ft. During the decade from 1992-2002, 3,400 volunteers donated 50,000 hours of time to construct the Sciencenter. In 2010, the Sciencenter acquired an additional 8,000 sq. ft. building to support its growing traveling exhibition program. Today, the Sciencenter is a nationally recognized museum, hosting 100,000 guests in Ithaca each year and reaching over 1.5 million guests worldwide through our traveling exhibitions and outreach programs. The Sciencenter is accredited by the American Alliance of Museums (AAM) and is a member of the Association of Science-Technology Centers (ASTC) and Association of Children's Museums (ACM).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes log notebooks from Executive Director Charles Trautmann, annual reports, meeting minutes, newsletters, calendar of events, manuals and brochures of the Sciencenter.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Sciencenter; Trautmann, Charles.
Subjects:
Science museums--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Museums--Educational aspects.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Governance
Series II. Newsletters
Series III. Minutes of Meetings
Subseries IIIa. Staff
Subseries IIIb. Board Meetings (Trustees, Advisory)
Series IV. Reports and Plans
Series V. Manuals, Handbooks, Notebooks
Series VI. Audit and Tax Files
Series VII. Accreditation Files
Series VIII. Exhibit and Education Files
Series IX. Brochures and Calendars
Series X. Retreats
Series XI. Other committees
Series XII. Media mentions
Series XIII. Awards/certificates
Series XIV. Miscellaneous
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Governance
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Charter Documentation: Original (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Charter Documentation: Recharter (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mission Statements (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ASTC governing membership review materials, 1 of 2, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - ASTC governing membership review materials, 2 of 2, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Board of trustees bylaws, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Hiring of the first ED, 1990-07-1990-10 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Charles Trautmann contracts, 1992-01-2011-07 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Exec dir. reviews, 1990-1999 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Charles Trautmann reviews, 1999-2009 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Charles Trautmann reviews, 2010-2016 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Board lists, 1993-2016 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Series II. Newsletters
  - Volunteer Newsletter, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Volunteer Newsletter, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Volunteer Newsletter, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Email Newsletters, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sciencenter News, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sciencenter News, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sciencenter News, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Sciencenter News, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sciencenter News, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sciencenter News, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Sciencenter News, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sciencenter News, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sciencenter News, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Sciencenter News, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Sciencenter News, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Sciencenter News, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - eNews, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - eNews, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - eNews, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - eNews, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - eNews, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - eNews, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Sciencenter Spectrum, 2010-2016 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - eNews, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - eNews, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - eNews, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - eNews, 2016 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Series III. Minutes of Meetings
  - Subseries IIIa. Staff
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Staff meetings, 1 of 2, 1993-2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Staff meetings, 2 of 2, 1993-2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Staff meetings, 1994-2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Staff meetings, 1 of 2, 2002-2006 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Staff meetings, 2 of 2, 2002-2006 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Staff meetings, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Staff meetings, 2011-2017 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Subseries IIIb. Board Meetings (Trustees, Advisory)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Advisory Board Minutes, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Advisory Board Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - From board meeting 91-95 binder, 1982-07-02, 1990-03-1990-12 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Board notes, 1991-01-1991-12 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Board notes, 1992-01-1992-12 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Board notes, 1993-01-1993-12 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Board notes, 1994-01-1994-12 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - From board meeting 91-95 binder, 1995-01-1995-11 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Board meetings, 1 of 2, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Board meetings, 2 of 2, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Board meetings, 1 of 2, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Board meetings, 2 of 2, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Board meetings, 1 of 2, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Board meetings, 2 of 2, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Board meetings, 1 of 2, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Board meetings, 2 of 2, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Board meetings, 1 of 2, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Board meetings, 2 of 2, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Board meetings, 1 of 2, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Board meetings, 2 of 2, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Board meetings, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Board meetings, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Board meetings, 1 of 2, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Board meetings, 2 of 2, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Board meetings, 1 of 2, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Board meetings, 2 of 2, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Advisory board meetings, 1 of 2, 1992-2010 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Advisory board meetings, 2 of 2, 1992-2010 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Advisory board meetings, 2011-2016 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Series IV. Reports and Plans
  - Annual Reports, 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Annual Reports, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Annual Reports, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Annual Reports, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Annual and 5-Year Work Plan, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Annual and 5-Year Work Plan, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Annual and 5-Year Work Plan, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Annual and 5-Year Work Plan, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Annual and 5-Year Work Plan, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Annual and 5-Year Work Plan, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Annual and 5-Year Work Plan, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Strategic and annual work plans, 1 of 3, 1987-2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Strategic and annual work plans, 2 of 3, 1987-2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Strategic and annual work plans, 3 of 3, 1987-2005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Strategic and annual work plans, 1 of 3, 2006-2017 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Strategic and annual work plans, 2 of 3, 2006-2017 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Strategic and annual work plans, 3 of 3, 2006-2017 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Long range planning committee, 1 of 3, 1998-2003 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Long range planning committee, 2 of 3, 1995-2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Long range planning committee, 3 of 3, 1995-2006 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - SC reports, 2005-2016 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Museum assessment program grant, supplemental materials, 1 of 3, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Museum assessment program grant, supplemental materials, 2 of 3, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Museum assessment program grant, supplemental materials, 3 of 3, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Scienceworks program, 2008-2010 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Annual report, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Financial reports, 1992-2002 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Series V. Manuals, Handbooks, Notebooks
  - 5-Year Business Plans, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 5-Year Business Plans, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 5-Year Business Plans, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Marketing Study (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Manual (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Staff Handbook (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Hiring Procedures Manual, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Emergency and Disasters Manual, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Volunteer Handbook (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Front Desk Procedures (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - YouthALIVE! Handbook, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Financial Planning Manual (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors Notebook, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Board and Staff Notebook, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board notebook, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Greeter handbook, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Safety manual, 2009-01 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Hiring manual, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Staff handbook, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Notebooks, 1990-1996; Trautmann, Charles (Box 7)
  - Notebooks, 1997-2001; Trautmann, Charles (Box 8)
  - Notebooks, 2002-2008-06-22; Trautmann, Charles (Box 9)
  - Notebooks, 2008-06-23-2016; Trautmann, Charles (Box 10)
- Series VI. Audit and Tax Files
  - Financial Audit, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Financial Audit, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Facilities Audit, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - IRS 501 (c) Letter, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - IRS Tax Form (I-990), 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - IRS Tax Form (I-990), 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - NYS Tax Return (CHAR-497), 1992-1999 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - NYS Tax Return (CHAR-497), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Audit Reports, 1 of 2, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Audit Reports, 2 of 2, 1989-1996 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Financials, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Financials, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Financials, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Financials, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Financials, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Financials, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Financials, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Financials, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Financials, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Financials, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Financials, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Financials, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Financials, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Financials, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Financials, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Financials, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Financials, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Financials, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Financials, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Financials, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Financials, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Financials, 2011-2014 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Museum Assessment Program (MAP) notebook, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Trademark registration, 1993-03-02 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Series VII. Accreditation Files
  - Accreditation Self-Study, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Accreditation Attachments, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Accreditation Attachments, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Accreditation Attachments, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Accreditation Updates, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Accreditation attachments, 1 of 2, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Accreditation attachments, 2 of 2, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Accreditation attachments, 1 of 2, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Accreditation attachments, 2 of 2, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Updates to accreditation materials, 1999-08 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Series VIII. Exhibit and Education Files
  - Exhibit Guide (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Exhibit Guide (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Exhibit Design Guidelines, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Sagan Planet Walk Education Materials (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Exhibits committee, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Exhibits committee, 1992-1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Exhibits committee, 1 of 2, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Exhibits committee, 2 of 2, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Exhibits committee, 2002-2007 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Sagan planet walk passports, 1997-2008 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Sagan planet walk - publicity, 1997-1998-12 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Sagan planet walk - student guide, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Sagan planet walk - funding, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Sagan planet walk - dedication plans, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Sagan planet walk - exhibit, original documents, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Alpha Centauri - early tries, 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Sagan planet walk - audio tour, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Sagan planet walk - asteroid station, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Sagan planet walk - Alpha Centauri station - Hawaii, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Sagan planet walk - commons rebuild, 2016 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Sagan planet walk - signage update to stations, 2016 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Series IX. Brochures and Calendars
  - Visitor Brochures (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Membership Brochures (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Corporate Membership Brochures (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Volunteer Brochures, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Education Brochures (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Sagan Planet Walk Cards (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Campaign Materials, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Campaign Materials, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Event Brochures (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Calendar of Events, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Calendar of Events, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Brochures and membership materials, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Membership/donor materials, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Monthly calendar/volunteer voice, 1 of 2, 1999-2005 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Monthly calendar/volunteer voice, 2 of 2, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Calendars, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Calendars, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Calendars, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Calendars, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Calendars, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Calendars, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Calendars, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Calendars, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Sciencenter monthly calendar, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Sciencenter monthly calendar, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Sciencenter monthly calendar, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Sciencenter monthly calendar, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Sciencenter monthly calendar, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Sciencenter monthly calendar, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Sciencenter monthly calendar, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Sciencenter monthly calendar, 2016 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Series X. Retreats
  - Board/Staff Retreats, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Board/Staff Retreats, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Board/Staff Retreats, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Retreat, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Retreat, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Retreat, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Series XI. Other committees
  - Finance committee, 1 of 2, 1999-2009 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Finance committee, 2 of 2, 1999-2009 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Executive committee, 1 of 2, 1991-2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Executive committee, 2 of 2, 1991-2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Human resources committee, 1 of 2, 1995-2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Human resources committee, 2 of 2, 1995-2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Earnec income task force, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Interface group minutes and plans, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Visitorship task force, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Phase III building advisory group, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Birthday build, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Deveopment committee, 1 of 2, 1990-2008 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Deveopment committee, 2 of 2, 1990-2008 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Sciencenter construction steering committee, 1989-02-1992-05 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Events committee, 1992-03-1992-11 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Human resources committee, Spring 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Committee development, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Committee exhibits, 1990-02-1992-05 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Committees - general, 1991-04-1992-01 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Landscaping, 1992-09-1994-04 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Membership, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Committee program, 1992-02-1992-05 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Committee - educational outreach, 1991-02-1993-01 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Education committee, 1991-02-1994-02 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Education committee, 1991-2013 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Trends, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Plan - strategy map, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Plan - scorecard, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Plan - active tasks, 2004-2006 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Plan - Miller notes, 2005-02-2007-04 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Series XII. Media mentions
  - Misc. early articles, 1985-08, 1988-10, Fall 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Flyers, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Archives, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Archives, 1991-1997 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Archives, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Archives, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Archives, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Archives, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Archives, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Archives, 2008-2009 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Archives, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Archives, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Archives, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Archives, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Archives, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Archives, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Archives, 2016 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Archives, 2017 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Series XIII. Awards/certificates
  - NYS legislative resolution regarding 25th anniversary of the Sciencenter, 2008-02-28 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Congressional proclamation - Cecelia Montanger-Vargas Spirit of Inclusion Award, 2017 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Series XIV. Miscellaneous
  - Syracuse Discovery Center correspondence, 1985-10-1986-12 (Box 12, Folder 11)